{
    "id": "9f60c60d770740f6b3122c623cba4a4b",
    "title": "Intermediate Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is so ……………………. that no one knew whether he enjoyed the party or not.",
            "description": "Taciturn means reserved or tight-lipped",
            "answers": [
                "garrulous",
                "loquacious",
                "taciturn"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………….. his brothers out of their inheritance.",
            "description": "To swindle is to cheat.",
            "answers": [
                "flummoxed",
                "swapped",
                "swindled"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He had a ………………………… outlook on life.",
            "description": "Sanguine means optimistic, hopeful.",
            "answers": [
                "sagacious",
                "salacious",
                "sanguine"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Regular exercise is ……………………………",
            "description": "Salubrious means healthy.",
            "answers": [
                "sagacious",
                "salubrious",
                "deleterious"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We pray that the court will reach a …………………….. decision.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sanctimonious",
                "sacrilegious",
                "sagacious"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He was a ……………………… tyrant.",
            "description": "Ruthless means unmerciful.",
            "answers": [
                "ruthless",
                "lenient",
                "remorseful"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………… on the courses of action open to him.",
            "description": "To ruminate is to contemplate or ponder.",
            "answers": [
                "rummaged",
                "collaborated",
                "ruminated"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is so ………………………… that his troubles never seem to get him down.",
            "description": "Resilient means rebounding or rapidly recovering.",
            "answers": [
                "resilient",
                "flaccid",
                "preposterous"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Just when I thought he had recovered, he suffered a ……………………….",
            "description": "Relapse means return to illness.",
            "answers": [
                "relapse",
                "remission"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Our relationship is based on ……………………………… respect.",
            "description": "Reciprocal means mutual or shared.",
            "answers": [
                "equivocal",
                "unilateral",
                "reciprocal"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The ……………………………. youth needed more understanding teachers.",
            "description": "Recalcitrant means stubborn.",
            "answers": [
                "redundant",
                "recalcitrant",
                "compliant"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A victim of injustice is bound to be full of ……………………………",
            "description": "Rancor means ill will or bitterness.",
            "answers": [
                "rupture",
                "rancor",
                "amity"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}